So, regarding the theme of this exam, "you",
it's not just about lines and acting.
It requires chemistry built
on deep understanding and trust.
So next, we're going to have
a real-life survival chase battle.
You'll face the following challenges.
There are five teams here,
each representing a color.
In the first-floor atrium, there are balloons in five colors.
The balloons cannot leave the first-floor atrium.
When you pop the balloon of your team's color,
then your team,
unlocks three minutes of Free Hunt.
During the hunt,
if you tag someone's torso,
you can take their wristband.
After being tagged,
they get a thirty-second cooldown time to run away.
Everyone wears three wristbands
in their team's color on the left hand.
Wear the wristbands you got from the pursuit on your right wrist.
When your left-hand wristbands run out,
you're out.
Collect wristbands of all four other colors to win.
And the winner's prize
is that your suitcase
will be returned to you.
I really want that.
I really, really want that.
This is a fight worth having.
This one's really hard to get.
So little time.
No face towel.
Got a face towel.
So embarrassing.
It keeps falling.
That's all there is.
Keep it safe for now.
Next, we'll take you
to various spots around the building.
Gu Jiacheng will pop the first balloon
in the lobby to start the game.
Go.
Come on.
I think we should stay here first,
and then I'll open the door halfway later.
If I hear a sound or
I hear footsteps, I can run,
maybe I'll just stay upstairs.
He goes down to pump the balloon,
or I start pumping first.
Then one person goes hunting,
and the other tries to find a chance.
Or how about I'm the one pumping the balloon?
Because honestly, I don't have much stamina.
Your stamina isn't great, is it?
Okay, then I'll do the running.
And I think another good thing about this spot
is that the echo over here is really loud.
If...
See you.
Is it really that easy to find?
How about we go over there?
That spot isn't easy to spot.
Why don't we just lie down here?
Underneath.
Okay.
The two of us can hide under that table
like two snails.
We're definitely winning today.
Today, our only strategy is to hide,
hide till the very end.
Our strategy now is for me
to stall Mr. Gu first.
Then let my other teammate
hurry downstairs and pump the balloon.
Let's switch quickly.
Honestly, I don't know what he's up to.
He might go team up with Senior,
then we can take everyone else out.
I can't figure out what his strategy is.
For some reason, Wang Ruijian and I
have zero chemistry.
We originally wanted to hide.
Lay low.
But I told him,
“Forget it. Let's not hide anymore.”
That's too cowardly.
Chen Zhixuan is nowhere to be found.
We were on mics,
but we didn't work well together.
Countdown.
Three, two, one.
Game starts.
It's now the Orange Team's Hunt Time.
Because I'm on my own.
I have to defend,
and attack at the same time.
Whoever gets close to me,
that's who I'll catch.
Take the elevator down to the third floor.
He keeps circling that room.
There's no way to get over there.
Nothing at all.
Hurry downstairs.
Go.
Back to the third floor to pop the balloons.
Pop the balloons directly?
Yes.
Oh no.
Come back.
He's going downstairs.
It's fine.
He's coming.
Go.
I saw Senior go downstairs,
so Ziyu and I split up and ran.
We wanted to avoid Senior,
and pop the balloons.
As soon as I got downstairs,
I saw Ziyu was closest to me.
I originally wanted to catch Ziyu.
But when I turned around, Sun Mingyang was holding a big balloon,
right on the other side.
I was afraid he'd pop the balloon right away,
run back up and counter-kill me.
So I had to stop him.
The balloon can't be taken out.
Here, take this.
Okay.
Orange Team gets a pink wristband.
We're done for.
Sun Mingyang got caught.
Our team doesn't have a single wristband left.
Orange Team's Hunt Time has thirty seconds left.
Senior was really close to me at the time,
and I never expected he locked onto me at first glance.
I thought maybe I could pull off a dodge-and-run,
so I tried to circle around him.
But Senior was just too fast.
It's pink again.
Orange Team gets its second pink wristband.
Orange Team has ten seconds of game time left.
Go.
Go pump the balloon.
Orange Team's Hunt Time is over.
I couldn't reach Chen Zhixuan at the time,
so there was no other way.
Since I couldn't reach him,
I had to rely on myself
to see if there was any chance
to get the balloon inflated.
Buy some time
for Chen Zhixuan and me.
Hurry.
That's not my pump.
Pump it fast.
He ran.
This doesn't feel good.
I'm out of here.
Now it's the Green Team's Hunt Time.
He can see both of us.
It popped again.
Now it's the Green Team's Hunt Time.
At the time, we knew that
popping the balloon made us the hunters.
So we went after that goal
and popped them one after another.
We could stay hunters forever.
They found a bug.
They could extend their time endlessly.
I figured it out.
Yep.
Green Team.
Go.
Quick.
I looked at the classroom on the right,
and a blue figure flashed in.
I couldn't run anymore by then,
so I just went into the classroom to take a chance.
Don't go.
You've got one of my colors already.
Didn't expect him to spot me
the moment he walked in.
He caught me again.
My second life.
The third time.
I was still wandering around that floor,
trying to find Wang Ruijian,
and then the thirty seconds were up.
Bai caught me one more time.
What's the point of taking me out?
You win with wristbands of four colors.
Even if he got all my wristbands,
it means nothing to him.
I realized I'm someone who doesn't understand the game rules.
You know?
I mistakenly thought the more wristbands you had,
the better your chances of winning.
I caught one after another,
my arm got tired from swinging,
and it turned out to be useless.
How about this.
Let's swap.
I can't go on. I'm too tired.
What's the point of making me out?
Let's swap.
We're going upstairs.
Green Team, thirty seconds left in Hunt Time.
Go down three floors. We have to grab the balloons now.
Go.
How about later.
Wait a second.
Let me catch my breath.
Green Team's Hunt Time is over.
During the chase,
my mic accidentally fell off and slid away.
And after that,
I never got in touch with Chen Zhixuan again.
Okay, now it's the Pink Team's Hunt Time.
They switched players.
The chase is on.
Pink Team.
Who's on the Pink Team?
He runs so fast.
I can't take it.
Who's on the Pink Team?
We plan to let them fight each other
while we reap the benefits.
"Kill" him.
He's got a "knife".
Only one thing on my mind.
I have to catch him.
I can't let down my teammates for the time they bought us.
After I caught him,
turns out he's this tall.
I can't believe I'm still alive.
He's got some nerve too.
Zhang Ziyu, you're awesome.
Are you tired? I can run a bit.
It's fine.
We've got it easy here.
Let's rest a bit.
Now it's the Blue Team's Hunt Time.
Now it's the Orange Team's Hunt Time.
Now it's the Pink Team's Hunt Time.
Hurry up.
We're the wolves.
Got him.
Ten minutes left in the game.
I think it's about time.
Let's go.
Let's go out for a walk.
Let's go pop some balloons.
Get out quick.
Run!
Oh no,
the air pump is gone.
I'll do it.
Use it freely.
You pump too.
The air pump is gone.
Oh no.
Blow it up.
Take it and blow.
Didn't we run out?
He went over all cocky.
Time's up.
It's up.
Now it's the Yellow Team's Hunt Time.
Whoever gets touched first.
Sun Mingyang is eliminated.
Yellow Team, send one up.
Alliance.
The three of us.
Sure.
Blue, Orange, Green.
Okay.
Deal?
We don't take each other out first.
Sure.
Take out everyone else first.
Sure,
because we've only got one player left.
Okay.
The three of us make a perfect three-person team, deal?
Sure.
Take out the balloon-pumper first.
I also found a bug.
I can keep stepping on balloons for Hunt Time,
so we can keep catching people,
So that's how I kept extending my time.
They found a bug.
They could extend their time endlessly.
I figured it out.
One person finds a chance to pop balloons.
One person finds a chance to catch.
As soon as he saw me going to pop balloons,
he'd start catching.
We were super in sync.
He's downstairs popping balloons.
I was upstairs chasing people,
then I thought, no way.
I can't catch anyone on my own,
so I used a lot of little tricks.
Ready?
I was always at that fire escape.
At the fire escape,
I caught Xiaomeng.
Then I came out of the bathroom,
and ran right into Senior.
Ziyu.
I tricked him too, saying,
there were hunters behind him.
Run!
Someone's over there.
Run, someone's over there.
Got him!
He got away.
Who's on the Pink Team?
Let me catch my breath.
Green Team's Hunt Time is over.
I feel like this isn't much fun anymore.
Let's go chase people down.
I'm done playing.
Over there.
You go over there.
I'll block them on the second floor.
Zhou Guorui is coming up the emergency stairs.
Let's block them together.
Yellow Team's Hunt Time is over.
Forty seconds left.
The countdown had already started,
so I panicked.
Anyway, I went all in burning my bridges.
Yellow Team, ten seconds until the game ends.
Hurry.
Wait, no.
Yellow Team, thirty seconds until the game ends.
He went downstairs.
No wait.
How's he blowing it up so fast?
Quick.
Step on it.
Step on it now!
Catching me would've been just one reach away.
That's how close it was.
Quick.
Now it's the Yellow Team's Hunt Time.
Later I thought, forget it,
maybe I'll just give up,
because I really couldn't run anymore.
Game over.
Surviving till the end is winning.
The winner takes all.
There was really nothing I could do.
So smart.
He was really so smart back then.
But his athletic ability is really strong.
He caught so many people in one go.
I really didn't expect that.
So amazing.
There's a real kind of chemistry between us.
In a lot of situations,
we were both thinking the same thing,
so the final winners are Ma Weixian,
and Zhou Guorui.
Let's present our prize,
A big gift.
A suitcase.
So jealous.
Nice, bro.
That's awesome.
Thank you everyone.
Great work, everyone.
You really worked hard.
Senior, is there anything you'd like to say to everyone?
I think,
there's no need to use words
to express too much to you all.
Since you've chosen this profession,
I believe you all truly love it.
Each of you has your own strengths.
In the future, in this industry,
you must learn to 'go down' a little.
Put your focus,
put your thoughts,
put even your energy into understanding this world,
understanding this society,
understanding the relationships between people.
I also hope everyone gets better and better.
Keep going.
Thank you, Senior.
Three, two, one.
Okay, thank you, teachers.
Thank you, Senior.
Thank you.
Great work, everyone.
Learn the sounds and tones, distinguish the four tones.
The four tones must be clearly distinguished.
Get ready to breathe in.
Exhale and rise.
Begin.
One.
Everyone up.
Five, six, seven.
Go.
Come with me.
I'm not going.
Not going.
I'll stay with you till the end of time.
Forever.
Stand up straight.
Repeat.
Right.
Again.
Waiter.
Chicken feet and pork ribs rice.
No scallions.
Hold it.
Hold it a bit longer.
Good.
It's getting richer and richer.
This part is good.
This part is fun.
Alright, class dismissed.
Thank you, teachers.
Thanks for your hard work, teachers.
Stop spraying, it hurts like crazy.
Let me try one too.
Wait, don't move.
Okay.
What are you laughing at?
Do you know what he just did?
I just wanted to see how you drew this.
Learn a trick or two.
You go first, show it.
I'm already ready.
This one is mine.
My dear Guorui.
How is it?
It's hideous.
Time to show mine.
Looks good, right?
It's actually pretty good.
It's so vivid.
It really does.
Bro, which one do you think looks better?
Look at this.
This is the one, right?
Bro, pick again.
As a partner, the thing I value most
is instantly following up in a team fight.
I think we need to have chemistry.
And he and I,
really do have great chemistry.
I feel like he's
the most in-sync partner I've met so far.
I feel like both of us
are kind of easygoing people,
pretty quirky.
When I first saw him,
I thought he seemed pretty distant.
But after filming for a few days,
I realized,
he is really quirky.
I just want to explore
his inner world more,
especially the intellectual and spiritual aspects.
As for me,
I'm someone
whose mindset is always changing.
Before high school,
I was always studying really hard.
My grades were excellent.
I was only 30 points short of a perfect score
on the high school entrance exam.
And then...
So impressive!
Then after starting high school,
because I couldn't quite keep up academically,
I switched to painting.
Then in college,
I got involved with the drama club,
and some student film crews.
That's when I got
the idea of becoming an actor.
Now that I'm an actor,
I might keep painting in the future,
but I'll keep trying new things.
I'll stay curious.
Actually, you have a really strong sense of security.
I feel like I'm the opposite of you in that way.
Based on my experiences growing up,
I'd say I've been pretty anxious,
or my sense of security is basically zero.
Why did you take my guitar away?
Give it back.
Let me play it a bit.
You can't play.
You're gonna break my guitar.
No, how would I break it?
How could this thing even break?
Then teach me how to play.
Sure.
To play a C chord,
here, this finger of yours,
place it here.
This one.
Press it down, right?
Yes, press it down.
It hurts.
Hurting is right.
That meansl'm doing it right. Right?
Yes.
Pressing down tight. Don't slack off.
Come on.
No, I...
This...
I've never suffered like this in my whole life.
Well done, young master.
You've never suffered like this, huh?
Why are you being so dramatic?
Try it again.
No, press it down firmly.
Yes.
Press it further in.
Further in.
It's not going further in.
More.
I'm pressing it into my flesh!
Yes, keep going.
How is this any different from torturing me?
Look at you.
That's it.
Awesome.
Like this.
Just keep the beat for me, okay?
Can I do a freestyle rap?
Sure.
Now you go.
Think of a topic.
Sun Mingyang.
OK.
Come on.
I'll never forget,
that moment when you said,
you were standing next to option C.
I couldn't protest,
so I knew I had to pick you.
At the time I was really sad too,
and thinking about it kept me up at night.
So right now I can't sit here with you,
that's why I have to stand.
What should I do?
What do you mean you couldn't choose?
I didn't have a clear preference between them,
so I told you two to just do rock-paper-scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors.
So I won rock-paper-scissors, right?
Yeah, I'd rather leave it to fate.
And then we became partners.
I never thought I'd open up this fast,
you know?
You'll probably keep 'pretending' for a while.
I'm not 'pretending',
you know?
I just can't control myself.
When I talk to people,
I'm just the slow-to-warm-up type.
But you're able to get people
to trust you quickly.
Not one hundred percent trust,
but at least they show their truest selves.
Right?
Communicating with you,
talking with you like this.
So I honestly never thought,
we'd become partners.
You know?
It's just that your personality
seems totally different from mine,
I don't know why you came at me the first time.
But after you did that
it felt like maybe I could push back at you too.
And then, I gradually just started having fun with everyone.
Like, we don't have to be so careful.
Everyone just roasts each other.
We seem pretty close now,
I actually kinda enjoy it when he roasts me.
But Mingyang just comes at me that way,
and it makes me feel like
I can open up a little.
I think that's how Mingyang helped me
“tear” myself open a little,
the protective layer I keep over and use to shield myself,
making me more willing to be genuine,
and get along with everyone.
I want to ask you something.
I'm actually pretty curious
why did you choose
to be my partner?
I just felt like it was you.
I feel like you give off this mysterious vibe.
A bit "pretentious".
I mean, because I think, you give me a feeling,
that makes me want to explore you.
I want to get to know you more.
I think among the eight of us now,
you're the hardest one for me
to observe or explore.
You know what?
I chose to pair up with you,
because I recognize your professional skills.
But later on,
I actually felt like, if someone really chose me
out of all these people.
I just feel like
you choosing me would make me feel recognized.
I'm really happy
to have you as a good friend.
You're the first good friend I've made here.
I really cherish that.
I don't have many friends,
Then let's hug.
Let's hug.
Come on, a hug.
Have you never played basketball before?
I played as a kid.
I've been playing since I was seven.
I was pretty fierce.
Basketball was like a good friend to me,
How about this,
if you miss the shot,
truth or dare, okay?
Sure.
If you make it, I ask you,
if you miss, you ask me.
Sounds good.
Fine, go ahead and ask.
Out of the eight of us,
who do you think is the most handsome?
Me.
You can't pick yourself.
Don't be so cocky.
Then I think,
you.
Really?
Really.
Back when
you were picking teams,
when you found out you were in the same group as me,
what did you think?
I was actually pretty happy.
Why?
Because I felt like I got
someone I was more familiar with.
Why can't I make any shots today?
What was your first impression of my personality?
I think your personality
is actually a lot like mine.
You don't really talk that much.
You're relatively
more on the quiet side.
When we didn't know each other well, you didn't talk much.
But once we got close, we got really wild and rowdy.
For two people to become partners,
first of all, it's fate.
I feel like our personalities aren't complementary.
I feel like our personalities are actually pretty similar.
We're known as the least in-sync pair.
Whether it's eating,
or answering questions,
or doing anything else,
we both seem pretty out of sync.
I think what matters more is what kind of person this is
whether you two are
soul partners.
Among all the guys
Zhixuan is the one who
cares about me more.
He pays more attention to me.
When we talk, we're pretty in sync,
and we both feel great.
So the two of us think
the other is a really good person.